David Mozersky African Union High-Level Implementation Panel Papers MS205
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sudan Post-referendum negotiation files, 1998 -- 2012; MS205.004; 405 Digital Object(s)
  - Lead panel, 1998 -- 2012; MS205.004.00085
    - 2011-04-05 Economic neogtiations, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00226
      - Agendas, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00229
        - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Group - Addis Negotiation Tentative Agenda, 2010-04-10 -- 2011-04-06; MS205.004.00230
        - Draft Agendas for Economic Sub-Cluster Meetings in Ethiopia, 2010-04-05 -- 2010-04-08; MS205.004.00231
      - Final documents, 2011; MS205.004.00232
        - Assets and Liabilities, 2011; MS205.004.00233
          - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Cluster meeting Kuriftu II - Agreed Actions to Take Place Prior to Next Round, 2011-04-13; MS205.004.00234
          - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster - Distribution of Assets and Liabilities, 2011-04-09 -- 2011-04-10; MS205.004.00235; Laryea, Thomas
          - Bishoftu Round II - Sub-Cluster on Assets and Liabilities - Summary of Decisions, 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00236
          - Joint Committee on Trade and Related Payments Arrangements - Reflections on Some General Issues for Discussions, 2011-04-02; MS205.004.00237; Johnson, Omotunde E.G.
        - Communications, 2011; MS205.004.00238
          - Communications and Transportation Sub Group: Prioritization of Issues to be Agreed Upon Based on Urgency - Kuriftu, 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00239
          - Meeting of Communications and Transport Sub Group - Kuriftu, 2011-04-09; MS205.004.00240
          - Summary of the Communication and Transport Sub Group Meeting, 2011-05-05; MS205.004.00241
          - Terms of Reference for the Communications and Transportation Sub Group, 2011-04-09; MS205.004.00242
          - The Two Sudans - Trade and Related Payments Arrangements: Some General Issues for Discussion - Presentation, 2011-04-02; MS205.004.00243; Johnson, Omotunde E.G.
        - Currency, 2011; MS205.004.00244
          - Currency discussions, MS205.004.00245
          - Currency Discussions First Session 9 April - Minutes, 2011-04-09; MS205.004.00246
          - Currency Discussions Second Session 9 April - Minutes, 2011-04-09; MS205.004.00247
          - Currency Discussions First Session 10 April - Minutes, 2011-04-10; MS205.004.00248
          - Currency Discussions Second Session 10 April - Minutes, 2011-04-10; MS205.004.00249
          - Agreed Minutes of the Sub Group on Currency and Banking Kuriftu Resort, Bishoftu, Ethiopia, 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00250
          - Currency Discussions Third Session 11 April - Minutes, 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00251
          - Remarks on How to Deal with Currency in Circulating in South Sudan, 2011-04-14; MS205.004.00252
          - Terms and Conditions for Use of SDG's during the Transitional Period after 9 July 2011, 2011-05-05; MS205.004.00253
        - Economic, 2011; MS205.004.00254
          - Economic Cluster Workplan 10 April, 2011-04-10; MS205.004.00255
          - Economic Cluster Workplan 11 April, 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00256
        - Oil, 2011; MS205.004.00257
          - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster - Oil Sub Group - Douments Produced in Kuriftu 9-11 April 2011 (Joint Actions Agreed; Updated Roadmap for Oil Sub Group; Priority List of Issues; Disclosure; Draft Text for Settlement of Disputes and Ratification of Framework Agreement), 2011-04-09 -- 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00258
        - Water, 2011; MS205.004.00259
          - Second Round of Finance, Economic and Natural Resources Cluster Negotiations - Water Sub Working Group, 2011-04-09 -- 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00260
          - Request for High-Level Intervention from Water Sub Cluster, 2011-04-09; MS205.004.00261
    - 2011-05-16 Super group meeting, MS205.004.00262
      - Action Points for Sub Clusters, 2011-04-17; MS205.004.00263
      - Action Points for Sub Clusters, 2011-04-17; MS205.004.00264
      - Agendas, 2011; MS205.004.00265
        - Meeting of the Economic Super-Group - Annotated Agenda, 2011-05-19 -- 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00266
        - Meeting of the Economic Super Group, 2011-05-19 -- 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00267
        - Meeting of the Economic Super-Group - Final Annotated Agenda, 2011-05-19 -- 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00268
        - Talking Points for President Mbeki - Super-Group Opening Session, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00269
        - Economic Cluster Workplan, 2011-04-11; MS205.004.00270
      - Matrix, 2011; MS205.004.00271
        - Oustanding CPA and Post-referendum Issues, 2011-05-11; MS205.004.00272
        - Matrix of Preparations on Economic Issues (17/4/11), 2011-04-17; MS205.004.00273
        - Matrix of Preparations on Economic Issues (26/4/11), 2011-04-26; MS205.004.00274
      - Minutes, 2011; MS205.004.00275
        - NCP/GoS-SPLM/GoSS Post-2011 Referendum Arrangements Negotiations - Finance, Economic and Natural Resources Working Group (Cluster) - Guiding Principles, 2011-02-08; MS205.004.00276
        - Currency Discussions III: Summary Minutes - Kuriftu, Bishoftu, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00277
        - Currency Discussions III: Summary Minutes - Kuriftu, Bishoftu, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00278
        - Meeting of the Economic Super Group presentation, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00279
        - Meeting of the Economic Super Group - Presentation on Handling the Sudanese Pounds Circulating in the South, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00280
        - Mediation Strategy for CPA and PRA - Preparation for Final Negotiating Session - AUHIP Internal Confidential, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00281
        - Agenda for Economic Meeting of Lead Negotiating Panel - Kuriftu, Bishoftu, 2011-05-19 -- 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00282
        - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster - Oil Sub-Group - Position Paper/Status of Negotiations, 2011-05-11; MS205.004.00283
        - Points of Agreement May 19 and 20, 2011-05-19 -- 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00284
        - Points of Agreement May 19, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00285
        - Points of Agreement May 20, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00286
        - Status of all CPA Post-Referendum Negotiations Issues, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00287
        - Talking Points for President Mbeki - Super-Group Opening Session - May 19, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00288
        - Super-Group Meeting - Opening Session May 19 2011 - Minutes, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00289
        - Super-Group Meeting - Day 2, May 20 2011 - Minutes, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00290
        - Super-Group Meeting - Day 3, May 21 2011 - Minutes, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00291
        - Economic Meeting of the Lead Negotiating Panel - Kiriftu, Bishoftu - Minutes, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00292
        - Economic Meeting of the Lead Negotiating Panel - Kiriftu, Bishoftu - Minutes, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00293
        - Economic Meeting of the Lead Negotiating Panel - Kiriftu, Bishoftu - Minutes, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00294
        - Currency, 2011; MS205.004.00295
          - Currency Discussions: Summary Minutes - Kuriftu, Bishoftu, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00296
          - Currency Discussions: Short Summary Minutes (Not Agreed by Parties) - Kuriftu, Bishoftu, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00297
          - Currency Discussions: Summary Minutes (Confidential to Mediation, Not Agreed by Parties), 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00298
          - Currency Discussions: Agreed Summary, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00299
          - Meeting of the Economic Super Group - Presentation on Handling the Sudanese Pounds Circulating in the South, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00300
          - Meeting of the Economic Super Group - Presentation on Handling the Sudanese Pounds Circulating in the South (final version), 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00301
          - Report to Super-Group, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00302
        - Debt, 2011; MS205.004.00303
          - Debt and Assets Sub-Group- Minutes, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00304
        - Oil, 2011; MS205.004.00305
          - Spoken Presentation by Anders Hannevik - Minutes, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00306
          - Oil Options Paper - Presentation to Lead Panel by Anders Hannevik, 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00307
          - Points of Agreement May 19 and 20, 2011-05-10 -- 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00308
          - Letter from H.E. Pagan Amum (Chair SPLM/GoSS Negotiation Team) to Idriss Abdelgader (Chair GoS/NCP Negotiation Team) - Lifting, Marketing and Trading of South Sudan Oil, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00309
          - Access to and Ownership of Export Infrastructure - Submitted by SPLM/GoSS Negotiation Team, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00310
          - SPLM/GoSS Proposed Language on the Transportation System and Infrastructure (Intented for Insertion into the Emerging "Head of Agreement"/"Framework Agreement being developed in the Sub-Group on Oil), 2011-05-19; MS205.004.00311
        - Summary, 2011; MS205.004.00312
          - Letter from Thabo Mbeki (Chairperson AUHIP) to Idriss Abdelgader (Lead Negotiator GoS/NCP) - Summary of Economic Meeting in Kuriftu, 2011-05-26; MS205.004.00313
          - Letter from Thabo Mbeki (Chairperson AUHIP) to Minister Pagan Amum (Lead Negotiator GoSS/SPLM) - Summary of Economic Meeting in Kuriftu, 2011-05-26; MS205.004.00314
          - The Facilitator's Memorandum to the Parties, Following the First Session of the Super Group to Negotiate Economic Issues under Post-Referendum Negotiations -Kuriftu, 2011-05-25; MS205.004.00315
          - The Facilitator's Memorandum to the Parties, Following the First Session of the Super Group to Negotiate Economic Issues under Post-Referendum Negotiations -Kuriftu, 2011-05-24; MS205.004.00316
          - The Facilitator's Memorandum to the Parties, Following the First Session of the Super Group to Negotiate Economic Issues under Post-Referendum Negotiations -Kuriftu, 2011-05-25; MS205.004.00317
      - Mediation Strategy for CPA and PRA - Preparation for Final Negotiating Session - AUHIP Internal Confidential, 2011-05-21; MS205.004.00318
      - Options papers, 2011; MS205.004.00319
        - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Cluster - AUHIP Debt Options Paper, 2011-05-16; MS205.004.00320
        - Meeting of the Economic Super Group - Presentation on Handling the Sudanese Pounds Circulating in the South, 2011-05-20; MS205.004.00321
        - Options Paper on the Handling of Sudanese Pounds Circulating in the South, 2011-05-18; MS205.004.00322
        - Sudan Petroleum Economics - Presentation by Anders Hannevik, 2011-04-07; MS205.004.00323
        - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster - Oil Sub-Group - Options Paper, 2011-05-16; MS205.004.00324
        - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster - Oil Sub-Group - Options Paper, 2011-05-11; MS205.004.00325
      - Sub-group preparation meetings, 2011; MS205.004.00326
        - Proposed Schedule of Economic Cluster Meetings - April/May 2011, 2011-04-19; MS205.004.00327
        - Assets and Liabilities, 2011; MS205.004.00328
          - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Cluster - AUHIP Debt Options Paper, 2011-05; MS205.004.00329
          - Note on Assets and Liabilities for Sub-Cluster Meeting in Khartoum on May 8-9 2011, 2011-05-04; MS205.004.00330
          - Note on Assets and Liabilities for Sub-Cluster Meeting in (Khartoum) on (May 8-9 2011) - TWL Draft of April 28, 2011, 2011-04-28; MS205.004.00331
          - Note on Assets and Liabilities for Sub-Cluster Meeting in Khartoum on May 8-9, 2011, 2011-05-04; MS205.004.00332
        - Communications, 2011; MS205.004.00333
          - Summary of the Communication and Transport Sub-Group Meeting, 2011-05-05; MS205.004.00334
        - Currency, 2011; MS205.004.00335
          - Suggested Short Technical Questions for the IMF Regarding Currency and Banking Sub-Cluster Issues, 2011-05-03; MS205.004.00336
          - Joint Trade and Payment Arrangements Committee - Agreed Minutes, 2011-04-21; MS205.004.00337
          - Joint Trade and Payment Arrangements Committee - Verbatim Record, 2011-04-21; MS205.004.00338
          - The Republic of Sudan - Joint Committee on Trade and Related Payment Arrangements - Recommendations for a Framework Agreement to Promote and Facilitate Trade Between Sudan and South Sudan after 8th July 2011, 2011-04; MS205.004.00339
          - The Republic of Sudan - Joint Committee on Trade and Related Payment Arrangements - GOSS/SPLM Position Paper on the Recommendations for Promotion and Facilitation of Trade between Sudan and South Sudan after 9th July 2011, 2011-05-05; MS205.004.00340
          - Joint Trade and Payment Arrangements Committee 5 May 2011 - Minutes, 2011-05-05; MS205.004.00341
    - 2011-06-06 LNP final session, MS205.004.00342
      - Draft Joint Declaration on the Two Areas (Blue Nile and South Kordofan), 2011-06-14; MS205.004.00343
      - Framework Agreement between Government of Sudan and Sudan People's Liberation Movement (North) on Political Partnership between NCP and SPLMN, and Political and Securiting Arrangements in Blue Nile and Southern Kordofan States, 2011-06-28; MS205.004.00344
        The Agreement complements the Agreement on Cessation of Hostilities in Southern Kordofan, and guides the GoS and SPLMN in their future negotiations and will pave the way for comprehensive security and political arrangements in the Two Areas.
        Nīl al Azraq (Sudan); Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah (Sudan); Sudan--Politics and government; Sudan People's Liberation Movement-North
      - Agreement Between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation movement on Temporary Arrangements for the Administration and Security of the Abyei Area, 2011-06-20; MS205.004.00345
        The Agreement provides for temporary administrative arrangements for Abyei Area; demilitarization of the Abyei Area and for security to be provided by an Interim Security Force for Abyei (ISFA) consisting of Ethiopian forces.
        Internally displaced persons; Security; Armed forces; Sudan--Politics and government; Sudan People's Liberation Movement
      - Briefing for UN - AU Meeting, 2011-06-14; MS205.004.00346
      - AUHIP Report: Preparing for Two Sudans - A Future of Peace and Cooperation, 2011-07-08; MS205.004.00347
        Statement on the Status of Negotiations between the government of the Republic of the Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement.
        Abyei (Sudan); Nīl al Azraq (Sudan); Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah (Sudan); Sudan--Politics and government; Secession--South Sudan; Citizenship; Boundaries; Petroleum industry and trade; Peace negotiations; Currency; Sudan People's Liberation Movement
      - AUHIP Facilitators and Experts List, 2011-06-15; MS205.004.00348
      - Communique on the 18th Extra-Ordinary Session of the IGAD Assembly of Heads of State and Government on the Activities in Sudan, Somalia and Eritrea, 2011-07-04; MS205.004.00349
        Communique of 18th extraordinary summit of Heads of State and Government of the IGAD Assembly.
        Somalia; Eritrea; Sudan; Comprehensive Peace Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, Sudan People's Liberation Army (2005); Intergovernmental Authority on Development; African Union Mission in Somalia
      - Draft Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Minister Idriss Abdelgader - Invitation for Cluster Negotiatings Meeting, 2011-06-11; MS205.004.00350
      - Letter from H.E. Pagan Amum to Idriss Abdelgader - Follow Up on Commitments, 2011-05-22; MS205.004.00351
      - Agendas, 2011; MS205.004.00352
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 17, 2011, 2011-06-17; MS205.004.00353
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 17, 2011 - Day 2, 2011-06-18; MS205.004.00354
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 17, 2011 - Day 3, 2011-06-19; MS205.004.00355
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 17, 2011 - Day 4, 2011-06-20; MS205.004.00356
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 17, 2011 - Day 5, 2011-06-21; MS205.004.00357
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Addis Ababa, June 15-22, 2011, 2011-06-15; MS205.004.00358
        - Internal Draft Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 16, 2011, 2011-06-13; MS205.004.00359
        - Draft Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Super Group, 2011-06-11; MS205.004.00360
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 15, 2011 - For Parties, 2011-06-13; MS205.004.00361
        - Tentative Agenda for Interlinked Negotiations Commencing June 15, 2011 - For Parties, 2011-06-11; MS205.004.00362
      - Documents for presidents, 2011; MS205.004.00363
        - AUHIP Proposal for Interim Security Arrangements for Abyei, 2011-05-28; MS205.004.00364
        - Commentary on Abyei Proposal - AUHIP Internal Confidential, 2011-06-01; MS205.004.00365
        - Draft AUHIP Proposal for the Resolution fo the Status of Abyei Area, 2011-06-02; MS205.004.00366
        - Draft AUHIP Proposal for the Resolution fo the Status of Abyei Area - Referendum Option, 2011-06-02; MS205.004.00367
        - Proposed Post-CPA Joint Sovereignty Arrangements for the Abyei Area, 2011-06-06; MS205.004.00368
        - AUHIP Planning Meeting Agenda, 2011-06-06; MS205.004.00369
        - Security Cluster Meeting: Chiefs of Staff, Addis Ababa, 2011-06-05; MS205.004.00370
        - Fallback Arrangements to Ensure Stability in and around Abyei, 2011-06-07; MS205.004.00371
        - Final Round Strategy: Interlinked Negotiations, 2011-06-07; MS205.004.00372
        - Natural Linkages for Sequencing, 2011-06-03; MS205.004.00373
        - Security Negotiations Next Steps - AUHIP Internal Confidential, 2011-06-02; MS205.004.00374
        - Draft Sudan Security Summit Concept Note, 2011-06-05; MS205.004.00375
        - Overview Security Strategy, 2011-06-02; MS205.004.00376
        - Consolidated Proposal for Negotiations of the Political and Security Situation in the Two Areas (Blue Nile and Southern Korfodan States) - Declaration of Principles, 2011-06-01; MS205.004.00377
        - Political Framework and Joint Command Mechanism for the Two Areas (Blue Nile State and South Kordofan State) - Proposal to the Government of Sudan and the SPLKM/SPLA, 2011-06-01; MS205.004.00378
      - Minutes, 2011; MS205.004.00379
        - Sudan Final Negotiations - Minutes Opening Session June 17, 2011, 2011-06-17; MS205.004.00380
        - Water Cluster Group Notes, 2011-06-16; MS205.004.00381
        - AUHIP Bilateral Discussion with NCP on FTA - Minutes, 2011-06-18; MS205.004.00382
        - AUHIP Bilateral Discussion with SPLM on FTA - Minutes, 2011-06-18; MS205.004.00383
        - AUHIP Meeting with NCP, 2011-06-19; MS205.004.00384
        - NCP Proposal to AUHIP on Economi Shock in the North, 2011-06-19; MS205.004.00385
        - Super Group Meeting on Borders - Minutes, 2011-06-19; MS205.004.00386
        - AUHIP Bilateral Meeting with NCP - Minutes, 2011-06-19; MS205.004.00387
        - AUHIP Bilateral Meeting with SPLM on FTA - Minutes, 2011-06-21; MS205.004.00388
        - AUHIP Bilateral Meeting with Government of Sudan on FTA - Minutes, 2011-06-21; MS205.004.00389
        - FTA Meeting Presidents with SPLM and NCP - Minutes, 2011-06-27; MS205.004.00390
        - FTA Trilateral Technical Discussion - Minutes, 2011-06-27; MS205.004.00391
        - FTA Trilateral Technical Discussion - Minutes, 2011-06-28; MS205.004.00392
        - AUHIP Oil Negotiations - Minutes, 2011-06-28; MS205.004.00393
      - Preparation documents for panel, 2011; MS205.004.00394
        - Summary of Oustanding Negotiation Issues on FTAs, 2011-06-15; MS205.004.00395
        - Negotiations on Citizenship and the Rights and Freedoms of Common Nationals - Strategy Paper, 2011-06-14; MS205.004.00396
        - Talking Poins for Super Group Opening Session, 2011-06-15; MS205.004.00397
      - Proposals, 2011; MS205.004.00398
        - Assets and Liabilities, 2011; MS205.004.00399
          - Assets and Liabilities Opening Remarks - Super Group II Negotiating Round, 2011-06-17; MS205.004.00400
          - TWL Draft on Pensions - Contingency Option, 2011-06-13; MS205.004.00401
          - Government of Southern Sudan - Report on the Actuarial Valuation for South Sudan Members of the National Pension Fund, 2011-04; MS205.004.00402
          - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Cluster - Summary of Discussions, 2011-05-08 -- 2011-05-09; MS205.004.00403
        - Citizenship, 2011; MS205.004.00404
          - Citizenship and the Rights and Freedoms of Common Nationals - Agreement, 2011-06-15; MS205.004.00405
        - Currency, 2011; MS205.004.00406
          - Proposed Elements of the Draft Agreement on the Currency Issue, 2011-06-12; MS205.004.00407
        - Oil, 2011; MS205.004.00408
          - FTA Presentation - Oil Negotiations, 2011-06-15; MS205.004.00409
          - Draft Framework Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Government of the Republic of South Sudan / the Sudan's People's Liberation Movement - Concerning Transitional Financial Arrangements, Oil and Related Issues, 2011-06-20; MS205.004.00410
          - Final Draft Framework Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Government of the Republic of South Sudan / the Sudan's People's Liberation Movement - Concerning Transitional Financial Arrangements, Oil and Related Issues, 2011-06-20; MS205.004.00411
          - Financial Transition Arrangement Concept Note, 2011-06-14; MS205.004.00412
        - Water, 2011; MS205.004.00413
          - SPLM Draft Agreement between the Government of Sudan/National Congress Party and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement/Government of South Sudan on Cooperation on Transboundary Water Resources, 2011-06-17; MS205.004.00414
      - Security General Wilhelmson, 2011; MS205.004.00415
        - Annex A to Border Control/Border Security Organisation, 2011-06-07; MS205.004.00416
        - Point Paper on Border Security and the Light/Passive External Stakeholder, 2011-06-06; MS205.004.00417; Wilhemsen, Jan Erik
        - Annex A to SMAT in the Two Areas, 2011-06-09; MS205.004.00418
        - Annex B to SMAT in the Two Areas - JCM Tasks Broader Outline, 2011-06-09; MS205.004.00419
        - Point Paper on Border Security and the Light/Passive External Stakeholder, 2011-06-06; MS205.004.00420; Wilhemsen, Jan Erik
      - Strategy documents, 2011; MS205.004.00421
        - Agenda for June 4 - Lead Panel Negotiations, 2011-06-04; MS205.004.00422
        - Economic Issues to be Raised with the Presidency, 2011-06-11; MS205.004.00423
        - Final Round Strategy - Interlinked Negotiations, 2011-06-06; MS205.004.00424
        - Plans for Presidency Meeting(s), 2011-06-10; MS205.004.00425
    - Post-July Negotiations, 2011 -- 2012; MS205.004.00426
      - Framework Agreement between Government of Sudan and Sudan People's Liberation Movement (North) on Political Partnership between NCP and SPLMN, and Political and Securiting Arrangements in Blue Nile and Southern Kordofan States, 2011-06; MS205.004.00427
      - Draft Memorandum - Sudans Currency Issues, 2011-07-17; MS205.004.00428
      - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster - Agreed Minutes on Financial Issues Related to Transfers under the CPA, 2011-07-29; MS205.004.00429
      - Agreement on Border Monitoring Support Mission between the Government of Sudan and the Government of South Sudan, 2011-07-30; MS205.004.00430
        The agreement requests the UN to endorse the agreement on the Border Monitoring Support Mission with the following additional tasks to the UNISFA mandate: 1)Provide force protection; 2)Provide observers; 3)Provide logistic and air support; 4: Provide Accommodation for national observers.
        Abyei (Sudan); Borderlands; Boundaries; Demilitarized zone; United Nations Interim Security Force for Abyei